Guide to the International Brigades Archive, Moscow: Selected Images ALBA.PHOTO.177
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Folder 190: 15th International Brigade Volunteers, Unidentified
  - [Soldier outdoor portrait, rolling up right shirtsleeve], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190024)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/24
  - [Soldier with pointy moustache and goatee], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190025)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/25
  - [Soldier on motorcycle next to tree], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190026)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/26
  - [Low angle officer in full uniform], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190027)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/27
  - [Man doing repair work on a vehicle], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190028)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/28
  - [Man and two women together leaning against a stone wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190029)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/29
  - [Woman posing on hillside among large plants], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190030)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/30
  - [Wide shot man near barn, railroad tracks (?)], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190031)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/31
  - [Officer and woman seated on stone wall overlooking city], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190032)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/32
  - [Shirtless man, sandbag wall in background], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190033)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/33
  - [Soldier with shirt and jacket posed against stone wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190034)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/34
  - [Soldier posed against stone wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190035)
    Moscow Number: 5/19035/
  - [Shirtless man, sandbag wall in background], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190036)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/36
  - [Closeup portrait of clean-shaven soldier, slightly out of focus(small)], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190037)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/37
  - [Officer in uniform, paisley wallpaper behind him], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190038)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/38
  - [Man in cardingan on building's entrance steps], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190039)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/39
  - [Black man blurry portrait outdoors], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190040)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/40
  - [Man sitting in crude shelter made of sticks against a wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190041)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/41
  - [Tank, black soldier posing in front of it], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190042)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/42
  - [Soldier with pointy moustache and goatee wearing beret], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190043)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/43
  - [Men in massive formation for march down city street], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190044)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/44
  - [Soldiers in trench lining up a rifle shot], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190045)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/45
  - [Soldier looking out from improvised tent], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190046)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/46
  - [Man with cooking equipment at campground], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190047)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/47
  - [Man in suit seated at desk], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190048)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/48
  - [Extreme closeup soldier shadowy portrait], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190049)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/49
  - [Portrait soldier in beret with jacket], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190050)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/50
  - [Portrait man in leather jacket, tie], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190051)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/51
  - [Soldier next to wrought-iron fence], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190052)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/52
  - [Soldier portrait against stone wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190053)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/53
  - [Soldier portrait against stone wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190054)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/54
  - [Soldier with cap and vest], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190055)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/55
  - [Man in short-sleeved shirt writing at desk], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190056)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/56
  - [Soldier with hat, jacket, tie], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190057)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/57
  - [Man in buttoned-up short posed against wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190058)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/58
  - [Man in beret, jacket], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190063)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/63
  - [Man in white shirt seated against wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190064)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/64
  - [Shirtless man, sandbag wall in background], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190065)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/65
  - [Soldier in full uniform], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190066)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/66
  - [Soldier with beret smiling, arms crossed], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190067)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/67
  - [Man in short-sleeved shirt posed outdoors], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190068)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/68
  - [Dark-skinned soldier in beret], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190069)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/69
  - [Soldier posed against stone wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190070)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/70
  - [Black soldier posed against stone wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190071)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/71
  - [Soldier with wild hair], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190072)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/72
  - [Soldier in winter gear; hat, scarf, coat], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190073)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/73
  - [Soldier in sleeveless shirt], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190074)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/74
  - [Officer smiling closeup], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190075)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/75
  - [Soldier in trench at machine gun], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190076)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/76
  - [Soldiers in front of sign], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190077)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/77
  - [Seated portrait man in dark jacket], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190078)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/78
  - [Soldier outdoor portrait], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190079)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/79
  - [Soldier outdoor portrait], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190080)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/80
  - [Robed figure standing in front of buildings and walls], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190081)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/81
  - [Soldier in glasses portrait against wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190082)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/82
  - [Man posed in open doorway], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190083)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/83
  - [Silhouetted soldier with rifle, bayonet], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190084)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/84
  - [Soldier with pack crouched behind a rock], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190085)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/85
  - [Helmeted soldier lines up a shot over a stone wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190086)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/86
  - [Closeup man, shirt unbuttoned], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190087)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/87
  - [Smiling soldier holding a donkey], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190088)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/88
  - [Soldier with beret smiling], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190089)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/89
  - [Soldier in jacket painting at desk], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190090)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/90
  - [Soldier in uniform smoking a pipe], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190091)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/91
  - [Bald soldier writing lefthanded at desk], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190092)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/92
  - [Soldier outdoor portrait], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190093)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/93
  - [Man in suit with small moustache], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190094)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/94
  - [Man with equipment in trench], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190095)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/95
  - [Woman relaxing against a pile of brush, smiling], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190096)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/96
  - [Man in vest emerging from cave (?)], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190097)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/97
  - [Man pulling on his boots], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190098)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/98
  - [Closeup man with moustache, shirt open at top], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190099)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/99
  - [Closeup man in uniform], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190100)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/100
  - [Man with bandana around neck, arms crossed], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190101)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/101
  - [Portrait soldier outdoors], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190102)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/102
  - [Man in uniform seated under a tree], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190103)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/103
  - [Soldier portrait against wall small], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190104)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/104
  - [Soldier portrait against wall looking away], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190105)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/105
  - [Soldier outdoor portrait wearing beret], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190106)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/106
  - [Soldier portrait against wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190107)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/107
  - [Soldier portrait outdoors], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190108)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/108
  - [Soldier portrait outdoors, bandage (?) on neck], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190109)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/109
  - [Soldier portrait outdoors (hard to see)], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190110)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/110
  - [Two men in field, one bending down to pick something up off the ground], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190115)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/115
  - [Man seated reading in study, window open], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190116)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/116
  - [Man standing on top of a small cliff], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190117)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/117
  - [Man in beret sitting by tent entrance], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190118)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/118
  - [Soldier seated cleaning his rifle], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190119)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/119
  - [Soldier aiming a rifle], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190120)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/120
  - [Soldier with beard and beret], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190121)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/121
  - [Low angle soldier at a machine gun post], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190122)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/122
  - [Using a telephone in the field], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190123)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/123
  - [Classroom with men receiving instruction], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190124)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/124
  - [Bald man with leather jacket sitting against low wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190125)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/125
- Folder 191: 15th International Brigade Volunteers, Group Shots, Many Unidentified, 1937-1938
  - Brigade Runners with Special Wall Newspaper, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191001)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/1
  - 15th International Brigade Armory [men working at a table], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191002)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/2
  - [Troops seated on a bench], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191003)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/3
  - Rapid Fire [men operating a machine gun], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191004)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/4
  - Scouts, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191005)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/5
  - [High shot from stage (?) addressing crowd (hard to see)], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191006)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/6
  - [Troops on parade, crowd watching], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191007)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/7
  - [Officers, troops gather outside building], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191008)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/8
  - [Three men in front of house in swimsuits], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191009)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/9
  - [Three men at table with drinks, others pose in background], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191010)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/10
  - [Three men in swimsuits by palm trees], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191011)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/11
  - [Two men in swimsuits with soldier in uniform], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191012)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/12
  - [Men gathering outside a building], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191014)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/14
  - [Men in trench, one in front holding rifle], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191015)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/15
  - [Men walking around near a building], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191016)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/16
  - [Troops and woman with flag], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191017)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/17
  - [Men outside a doorway fortified with a sandbag wall on an empty city street], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191018)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/18
  - [Group of troops in trench], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191023)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/23
  - [Men posing with motorcycle], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191024)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/24
  - [Man and woman sitting, man holding a puppy], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191025)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/25
  - [Four officers meeting], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191026)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/26
  - [Two men talking and leaning against doorway], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191027)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/27
  - [Men relaxing against wall in trench], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191028)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/28
  - [Group shot, officers, men, women], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191030)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/30
  - [Troops marching down the road in both directions], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191031)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/31
  - [Large brigade group shot], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191032)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/32
  - [Troops seated resting on the open countryside, some standing (panoramic wide)], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191033)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/33
  - [Troops talking with man in white polo shirt], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191034)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/34
  - [Men working at cooking pot], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191035)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/35
  - [Friendly conversation between two soldiers], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191036)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/36
  - [High shot of men talking, others walking around], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191037)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/37
  - [Group pose], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191038)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/38
  - [Group pose], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191039)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/39
  - [Small group shot sitting along a path], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191040)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/40
  - [Group of men resting under blankets], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191041)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/41
  - [Improvised tent with men inside], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191042)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/42
  - [Two soldiers, one with hat, smiling], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191043)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/43
  - [Small group shot sitting along a path (mirror of 177-191 40)], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191044)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/44
  - [Men in swimsuits with uniformed soldier], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191045)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/45
  - [Soldiers pose by trees with man in shirt and tie], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191046)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/46
  - [Two men in berets pose in countryside], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191047)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/47
  - [Wide shot men walking along paved road. Palm trees in left of photo], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191048)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/48
  - [Two men, one with leather jacket, standing under a tree], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191049)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/49
  - [Soldier in cape, another man sitting in foxhole. Man on left talks on radio/phone], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191050)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/50
  - [Two officers pose in field], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191051)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/51
  - [Two officers pose in field, other visible], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191052)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/52
  - [Group shot in front of camp setup], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191053)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/53
  - [Two men sitting pose together], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191054)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/54
  - [Three men, one crouched, pose outdoors], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191055)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/55
  - [Large brigade group shot], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191056)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/56
  - [Two soldiers shaking hands], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191057)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/57
  - [Two soldiers, one smoking a cigarette], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191058)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/58
  - [Man in suit in a chair with two others standing beside him (bad focus)], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191059)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/59
  - [Standing group pose with one soldier sitting in front], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191060)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/60
  - [Two men posed against a brick wall], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191061)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/61
  - [Four men, one woman, one child, in front of a house], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191062)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/62
  - [Three men on hillside in front of a boulder], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191063)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/63
  - [Large brigade group shot, many men seated and standing], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191064)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/64
  - [Two officers, one with hat, other leaning on him], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191065)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/65
  - [Women visitor (?) with soldiers outdoor casual shot], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191066)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/66
  - [Group shot with men and women, forest background], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191067)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/67
  - [Group shot with several soldiers aiming rifles], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191068)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/68
  - [Six men sitting on stone bench by ivy-covered wall], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191069)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/69
  - [Three helmeted soldiers sit by shelter opening], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191070)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/70
  - [Men sit in charis on a patio reading newspapers], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191071)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/71
  - [Two men pose sitting in one chair], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191072)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/72
  - [Portrait of four men, one seated, one with arm sling], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191073)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/73
  - [Crouching group shot, low angle], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191074)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/74
  - Fire! A Reed Hut in Olive Grove Is in Flames as 15th International Brigadiers Rush to Put it Out, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191076)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/76
  - 15th International Brigade Comrades go for a Swim, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191079)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/79
  - Brigade Machine Gun Company [cleaning gear under a tree], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191083)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/83
  - Machine Gun Nest (Grandesa Front) [man aims a machine gun], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191085)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/85
  - Pozuela de las Torres [group of men and women, raised fists], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191086)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/86
  - Pozuela de las Torres [soldiers dug into a trench], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191087)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/87
  - [Woman poses in trench with group of soldiers, sandbag wall in background], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191096)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/96
  - [Troops lined up, being addressed by an officer], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191097)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/97
  - [Group of men looking out from a trench], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191098)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/98
  - [Groups of soldiers in town, mixing with townspeople], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191099)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/99
  - [High angle alleyway], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191100)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/100
  - Headquarters Kitchen (Jueves Labradas), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191101)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/101
  - [Large group shot, some men shirtless], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191104)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/104
  - [Group shot, men to right of frame standing], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191105)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/105
  - [Five men sitting on ground next to path, one standing and looking into the distance], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191106)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/106
  - [Wide shot large group shot], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191107)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/107
  - [Woman in trench among group of men], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191108)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/108
  - [Three soldiers against low wall], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191109)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/109
  - [Five soldiers pose in front of building/wall, three standing, two crouched], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191110)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/110
  - [Three men pose in front of trees], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191111)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/111
  - [Four men pose in the middle of a road, one smoking a cigarette], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191112)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/112
  - [Three men, two shirtless, cacti to left of frame], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191113)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/113
  - Otto Schumacher [men fire into the sky from a behind a bush], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191114)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/114
  - Captured Equipment, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191116)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/116
  - Front Line Trench (Jarama), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191117)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/117
  - [Two-row group shot, large portion of image cut out], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191118)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/118
  - Rifle Inspection, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191119)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/119
  - [Two men leaning against a doorway (copy of 177-191 27)], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191120)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/120
  - [Group shot pose framed to the left], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191121)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/121
  - [Men looking at papers on a desk, one smoking. Outside of a house, two using typewriters], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191122)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/122
  - [Group shot of seven men with caps and berets], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191160)
  - [Group of men seated in shade under trees], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191123)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/123
  - 15th International Brigade Anglo-American Section [one man cutting another's hair], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191124)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/124